Robert A. Taft Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1946-1953 (Box 871-1284)
  - 1952 (Box 1079)
    - Taxes
      - Inheritance (Box 1192)
      - Sales
      - Withholding
    - Television
    - Tennessee Valley Authority
    - Tobacco
    - Townsend Plan
    - Trade
    - Transfers, (3 folders)
    - Transportation
    - Treasury Department (Box 1193)
    - Treaties
    - Truman, Harry S.
    - Unemployment compensation
    - United Nations, (3 folders)
    - United World Federalists (Box 1194)
    - Universal military training
    - Veterans
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Hospitals
      - Legislation, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 1195)
      - Tryon, James E.
    - Visitors, (2 folders)
    - War Korea, (2 folders) (Box 1196)
    - War material, disposal
    - Water
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military Academy
    - Wildlife
    - Wool
    - Yale university, New Haven, Conn.
    - Yugoslavia
  - 1953 (Box 1197)
    - Agriculture, (3 folders)
    - Air force, (2 folders); (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 1198, Box 1199)
    - Airports
    - Alaska
    - Allotments
    - Appointments
      - General
        - A-C, (2 folders)
        - D-S, (5 folders) (Box 1200)
        - T-Z (Box 1201)
      - Executive, (2 folders)
    - Appropriations, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 1202)
    - Armed services, (2 folders)
    - Army assignments, A-Z, (5 folders) (Box 1203)
    - Army
      - Complaints, (2 folders)
      - Department of
      - General (Box 1204)
        - A-R, (6 folders)
        - S-Z, (2 folders) (Box 1205)
      - Pay
    - Articles
      - About Taft
      - Statements requested by Taft, (2 folders) (Box 1206)
      - Sent to Taft, (2 folders)
    - Atomic bomb
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 1207)
    - Autographs
    - Aviation
    - Award
    - Banking
    - Bids, government, (2 folders)
    - Biography (Box 1208)
    - Bonds
    - Books and booklets sent to Taft, (3 folders)
    - Budget, (2 folders) (Box 1209)
    - Business, general, (2 folders)
    - Butter
    - Cancer
    - Casualties
    - Census (Box 1210)
    - China
    - Christmas cards
    - Citizenship
    - Civil Aeronautics Administration
    - Civil defense
    - Civil rights
    - Civil service
    - Claims
      - A-D
      - E-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1211)
    - Clippings
      - General
      - Taft's Illness (Box 1212)
    - Clow, William E.
    - Coast guard
    - Commerce Department
    - Commission, (2 folders)
    - Committees (Box 1213)
    - Commodity Credit Corp.
    - Communism
    - Communists, (2 folders)
    - Condolence
    - Congratulation
    - Congress, Library of (Box 1214)
    - Congressional Directory
    - Congressional Record
    - Conscientious objectors
    - Contributions
    - Controls, (2 folders)
    - Cooperatives
    - Correspondence received during Taft's illness, (2 folders) (Box 1215)
    - Cotton
    - Course in Senate
    - Courts- martial, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 1216)
    - Currency
    - Customs
    - Deferments, (2 folders)
    - Displaced persons
    - District of Columbia (Box 1217)
    - Draft, (2 folders)
    - Durkin, Martin
    - Economic Report, Joint Committee on
    - Education
    - Education (Box 1218)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - Elections
    - Electoral College
    - Emmanuel, Victor, (3 folders)
    - Employment, executive (Box 1219)
    - Engagements, (4 folders)
    - England
    - Equal rights (Box 1220)
    - Exports and imports
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee
    - Fair Trade
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Federal Communications Commission, (2 folders)
    - Federal Housing Administration
    - Federal Power Commission (Box 1221)
    - Federal
    - Federal Reserve
    - Federal Security Agency
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Fisheries
    - Flag
    - Floods and flood control
    - Food
    - Football tickets
    - Foreign policy, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 1222, Box 1223)
    - France
    - Furloughs
    - Gallery panes
    - Germany
    - Gifts
    - Gold (Box 1224)
    - Government Printing Office
    - Great Britain
    - Greece
    - Hawaii, (2 folders)
    - Health
    - Highways
    - Hospitals
    - House joint resolutions
    - House of Representatives bills, nos. 0-6999, (8 folders) (Box 1225)
    - Housing, (6 folders) (Box 1226)
    - Hungary (Box 1227)
    - Immigration
      - A-R, (6 folders)
      - S-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1228)
    - Inaugural tickets
    - Inauguration, (2 folders) (Box 1229)
    - India
    - Indians
    - Inflation
    - Insurance
    - Intergovernmental relations
    - Interior, Department of
    - Internal Revenue Service, (2 folders) (Box 1230)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, (2 folders)
    - Introductory letters, (2 folders)
    - Invitations declined (Box 1231)
      - A-L, (6 folders)
      - M-T, (5 folders) (Box 1232)
      - U-Z, (2 folders) (Box 1233)
    - Japan
    - Jewish
    - Justice Department, (1 folder) (Box 1234)
    - Keller, O. E. M.
    - Klein, Julius
    - Korea
    - Labor
      - A-F, (3 folders)
      - G-Q, (7 folders) (Box 1235)
      - R-Z, (3 folders) (Box 1236)
    - Labor Department
    - Labor legislation, (2 folders)
      - A-B, (2 folders)
      - B-D, (5 folders) (Box 1237)
      - E-K, (6 folders) (Box 1238)
      - L-P, (6 folders) (Box 1239)
      - P-S, (5 folders) (Box 1240)
      - T-Z, (5 folders) (Box 1241)
    - Labor and Public Welfare Commission
    - Labor unions
    - Land grants
    - Langer, William
    - Legislation miscellany
      - A-B
      - C-S, (6 folders) (Box 1242)
      - T-Z (Box 1243)
    - Licenses
    - Livestock
    - Loans
    - MacArthur, Douglas
    - Marine corps
    - Martin, I. Jack
    - Meat
    - Membership
    - Merchant marines
    - Metals and minerals
    - Military discharges (Box 1244)
      - “A-H” miscellaneous, (6 folders)
      - “J-R” miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 1245)
      - Ross, A. L.
      - “S-Z” miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 1246)
    - Milk
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1247)
      - A-C, (4 folders)
      - C-G, (5 folders) (Box 1248)
      - H-L, (5 folders) (Box 1249)
      - L-O, (4 folders) (Box 1250)
      - P-S, (5 folders) (Box 1251)
      - T-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1252)
      - Get-well wishes, (2 folders)
    - Monetary (Box 1253)
    - Mutual Security Administration
    - National
    - National debt
    - National defense
    - National Guard
    - National Labor Relations Board
    - National parks
    - National Production Authority
    - Navy
      - A-N, (3 folders)
      - O-Z, (2 folders) (Box 1254)
    - Negroes
    - Newspapers
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization tax agreement
    - Office details, (2 folders)
    - Office of Price Stabilization, (2 folders)
    - Ohio (Box 1255)
      - Patronage
      - State matters, A-Z, (5 folders)
    - Oil
    - Pages (Box 1256)
    - Palestine
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Peace
    - Pensions
      - A-N, (3 folders)
      - O-Z, (2 folders) (Box 1257)
    - Philippines
    - Photographs, (2 folders)
    - Policy Committee
    - Political
      - Appointments
        - General (Box 1258)
          - A-N, (4 folders)
          - O-Z, (2 folders) (Box 1259)
      - Republican
        - A-G, (3 folders)
        - H-Z, (5 folders) (Box 1260)
      - Taft (Box 1261)
    - Positions
      - A-H, (6 folders)
      - J-S, (5 folders) (Box 1262)
      - S-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1263)
    - Postmasters
    - Post offices, (2 folders) (Box 1264)
    - Presidency
    - Private bills, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 1265)
    - Promotions
    - Propaganda
    - Public laws, miscellany
    - Public works
    - Publications
      - A-D, (4 folders)
      - E-M, (6 folders) (Box 1266)
      - M-S, (5 folders) (Box 1267)
      - T-Z, (2 folders) (Box 1268)
    - Puerto Rico
    - Radio
    - Railroad retirement
    - Railroads
    - Reciprocal trade agreements
    - Recommendations
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp. (Box 1269)
    - Religion
    - Reorganization plan
    - Republican National Committee
    - Reservations and tickets
    - Retirement legislation
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Rubber
    - Rural Electrification Administration
    - Russia (Box 1270)
    - Saint Lawrence Seaway
    - Salaries
    - Securities and Exchange Commission
    - Selective Service Act
    - Selective Service System
    - Senate bills (Box 1271)
      - Nos. 0-1999
      - Nos. 1000-5999, (4 folders) (Box 1272)
    - Senate resolutions
    - Senators
      - Correspondence about
      - Correspondence with
    - Small business (Box 1273)
    - Social security, (4 folders)
    - Social security legislation
    - Socialism (Box 1274)
    - Soil conversation
    - South America
    - Southern patronage problems
    - Spain
    - Speakers
    - Special bills
    - Speech comments
    - Speeches
      - Copies requested
      - Received from others
    - State Department, (2 folders) (Box 1275)
    - Steel
    - Strikes
    - Sugar
    - Supreme Court
    - Taft
      - Illness, (3 folders); (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box 1276, Box 1277)
      - Martin, I. Jack correspondence
      - Memorial
      - Taft, Martha Bowers
      - Taft, William Howard
      - Taft, William Howard III
    - Tariff
    - Tate, Ben E. (Box 1278)
    - Tax
      - Capital gains
      - Cooperative
      - Corporations
      - Excess profits
      - Excise
      - Exemptions
      - General, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 1279)
      - Income, (3 folders)
      - Miscellaneous
    - Television (Box 1280)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority
    - Tidelands
    - Tobacco
    - Townsend Plan
    - Trade
    - Trade agreements
    - Transportation
    - Transfers, individual cases
    - Transfers (Box 1281)
    - Treasury Department
    - Treaties, (2 folders)
    - Truman, Harry S.
    - United Nations, (1 folder) (Box 1282)
    - Universal military training
    - Veterans
      - Compensation
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Hospitals (Box 1283)
      - Legislation
    - Visitors, (2 folders)
    - Voting
    - Walter, Paul W.
    - War
      - Korea, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 1284)
      - Material, disposal of
    - Water, (2 folders)
    - Wenner, Thomas B.
    - Wheat
    - White House
    - Wool
    - Yale University, New Haven, Conn.
    - Yugoslavia
- Special Files, 1920-1953 (Box 1285-1290)
  Correspondence, statements, press releases, campaign literature, and election material concerning political activities and presidential nominations of Thomas E. Dewey, Dwight D. Eisenhower, Herbert Hoover, Harold E. Stassen, Adlai E. Stevenson (1900-1965), and Harry S. Truman.
  - Dewey, Thomas E. (Box 1285)
    - General, 1944-1948
    - Speeches, Republican National Committee, 1948
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - 1947-1952, (2 folders)
    - 1952-1953, (4 folders) (Box 1286)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1941-1948
  - Hoover, Herbert, and Robert A. Taft, 1920, (3 folders) (Box 1287)
  - Hoover campaign, 1928
  - Stassen, Harold E. (Box 1288)
    - General, 1945-1948, (4 folders)
    - Speeches, (2 folders) (Box 1289)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. (1900-1965), 1949-1952
  - Truman, Harry S.
    - General, 1948-1952, (2 folders)
    - Messages, 1945-1952 (Box 1290)
    - Speeches, 1945-1950, (3 folders)
- Speeches and Writings File, 1933-1953 (Box 1291-1336)
  Holograph and typewritten drafts, corrected proofs, and mimeographed copies relating to speeches, articles, books, and miscellaneous writings, including some by Martha Bowers Taft.
  Arranged chronologically and alphabetically thereunder by type of material.
  - 1934-1935 (Box 1291)
  - 1935
  - 1936, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 1292)
  - 1937
  - 1938
    - Debate, “New Deal Economy A failure”
    - Speech material
    - Speech, Republican convention
    - Statements
      - Dayton Coliseum, Dayton, Ohio
      - Newly elected senators
  - 1939
    - Addresses
      - American
        - Forestry Association
        - American Newspaper Publishers Association
      - Engineers' Union meeting
      - Foreign relations
      - Gridiron Club Dinner, Washington, D.C.
      - Howard University, Washington, D.C.
      - National Association of Life Underwriters
      - New Deal
    - Broadcast (Box 1293)
    - Releases
    - Remarks
    - Speeches
    - Statements and notes, (2 folders)
  - 1940 (Box 1294)
    - Addresses, (2 folders)
    - Articles, “This is my Husband,” by Martha Bowers Taft
    - Broadcast
    - Releases
    - Remarks
    - Speeches, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 1295)
    - Statements and notes
  - 1941
    - Addresses, (2 folders)
    - Articles
    - Broadcasts, (2 folders) (Box 1296)
    - Releases
    - Remarks
    - Speeches
    - Statements
  - 1942 (Box 1297)
    - Addresses
    - Articles
    - Broadcasts
    - Releases
    - Remarks
    - Speeches
    - Statement and notes, (1 folder) (Box 1298)
  - 1943
    - Addresses
    - Articles
    - Broadcast
    - Releases
    - Speeches
    - Statements and notes
  - 1944 (Box 1299)
    - Addresses
    - Articles
    - Broadcasts
    - Record
    - Releases
    - Remarks
    - Speeches, (2 folders)
    - Statements and notes, (4 folders) (Box 1300)
  - 1945 (Box 1301)
    - Addresses
    - Articles
    - Broadcasts
    - Remarks
    - Reports
    - Speeches
    - Statements and notes, (2 folders) (Box 1302)
  - 1946
    - Addresses, (2 folders)
    - Articles (Box 1303)
    - Broadcasts
    - Conference report, Price Control Act
    - Congressional Record, Fair Labor Standards Act of 1938
    - Engagement, University of Chicago Round Table, Chicago, Ill.
    - Excerpt, federal aid to education
    - Interview, American Forum of the Air Housing, Richard Harkness
    - Meeting, Executives Club, Chicago, Ill.
    - Releases
    - Remarks
    - Speeches and notes, (1 folder) (Box 1304)
    - Statements and notes
  - 1947
    - Addresses, (2 folders) (Box 1305)
    - Articles
    - Broadcasts
    - Releases
    - Remarks (Box 1306)
    - Speeches, (3 folders)
    - Statements and notes, (2 folders)
  - 1948 (Box 1307)
    - Addresses, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 1308)
    - Articles
    - Broadcasts
    - Releases, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 1309)
    - Remarks
    - Speeches, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 1310)
    - Statements and notes, (2 folders)
  - 1949 (Box 1311)
    - Addresses
    - Articles
    - Broadcast
    - Capitol Reports
      - Index and nos. 1-3
      - Nos. 4-34, (4 folders) (Box 1312)
    - Releases (Box 1313)
    - Remarks
    - Speech material, (2 folders)
    - Speeches
    - Statements
    - Washington Report (Box 1314)
      - Index and List
      - Nos. 1-28, (3 folders)
      - Complete set, 1949-1950
  - 1950 (Box 1315)
    - Addresses, (2 folders)
    - Articles
    - Broadcasts
    - Capitol Reports
      - Nos. 35-42
      - Nos. 43-60, (3 folders) (Box 1316)
      - Nos. 61-68, (2 folders) (Box 1317)
    - Press
      - Conference
      - Releases, campaign, (2 folders)
    - Radio program, nos. 1-10 (Box 1318)
    - Releases, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 1319)
    - Releases and proofs
    - Speech material, (3 folders) (Box 1320)
    - Speeches
    - Statements and notes (Box 1321)
    - Washington Report, Nos. 29-73, (2 folders)
  - 1951
    - Addresses, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 1322, Box 1323)
    - Articles
    - Broadcasts
    - Engagements, (1 folder) (Box 1324)
    - Lecture
    - Press conference
    - Releases
    - Speech material, (4 folders) (Box 1325)
    - Speeches (Box 1326)
    - Statements and notes, (4 folders)
  - 1952 (Box 1327)
    - Addresses, (4 folders); (3 folders) (Box 1328)
    - Articles
    - Engagements (Box 1329)
    - Releases
    - Speech material, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 1330)
    - Speeches, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 1331)
    - Speeches and notes
    - Statements and notes, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 1332)
  - 1953
    - Addresses
    - Broadcasts
    - Releases
    - Speech material, (2 folders) (Box 1333)
    - Speeches
    - Statements and notes
  - Undated (Box 1334)
    - Speech material
    - Article notes, (2 folders)
    - Notes, (3 folders)
    - Index (card files) (Box 1335)
    - Taft, Martha Bowers, (3 folders) (Box 1336)
- Business Papers, 1914-1953 (Box 1337-1383)
  Correspondence, business and property records, legal papers, certificates, statements, receipts, profit-loss trial balances, estate matters, check stub books, bank statements and canceled checks, and investment records.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material or name of person, organization, or subject.
  - American Bar Association, 1935-1938 (Box 1337)
  - American Law Institute, 1930-1938
  - Automobiles, 1942-1948
  - Ball, Mary, 1945-1947
  - Bookshelf, 1921-1928, (2 folders)
  - Bowers family, estate papers, 1943-1953
  - Burning Tree Club, Bethesda, Md., 1951-1953 (Box 1338)
  - Camargo Bank of Madiera, Madiera, Ohio, 1944
  - Camargo Club, Madiera, Ohio, 1938-1940, (2 folders)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, New York, N.Y., 1936-1940, (2 folders)
  - Central Trust Co., Cincinnati, Executive Committee, 1934-1938, 1948-1953 (Box 1339)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1942-1943, 1952
  - Cincinnati Chamber of Commerce, 1937-1938
  - Cincinnati Conservatory of Music, 1943
  - Cincinnati Country Day School, 1926-1939
  - Cincinnati matters, 1940-1945
  - Cincinnati Music Hall Association, 1943-1944 (Box 1340)
  - Cincinnati Street Railway Co., 1940-1943
  - Cincinnati Times-Star, 1941-1952
  - Corporation reports
    - 1950-1951
    - Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 1341)
    - Statements, 1943-1946, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 1342)
  - Covington and Cincinnati Bridge Co., 1942-1945
  - Dixie Terminal Building, Cincinnati
    - 1935-1942, (2 folders)
    - 1943-1946, (4 folders) (Box 1343)
    - 1947-1950, (3 folders) (Box 1344)
  - Edwards, Frances
    - 1943-1944
    - 1945-1952, (2 folders) (Box 1345)
  - Emery, Thomas J., memorial
    - 1941, (2 folders)
    - 1942-1946, (5 folders) (Box 1346)
  - Gruen Watch Co., 1935-1946, (2 folders) (Box 1347)
  - Indian Hill Acres, Cincinnati
    - 1925, 1933-1943, (2 folders)
    - 1944-1953 (Box 1348)
  - Koehl, William, Co., 1951-1947, (2 folders)
  - McNamara, Annie, estate papers, 1938-1939
  - Main Street property, 1944-1946
  - Manning, Helen Taft, Trust, 1938-1940 (Box 1349)
  - Messer, Frank and Sons, 1942-1953
  - New Indian Hill School, Cincinnati, 1922-1927
  - Ohio Chamber of Commerce
    - 1925-1926, (2 folders)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 1350)
  - Ohio Society of Washington, Washington, D.C., 1939-1940, (2 folders)
  - Receipts
    - 1917-1927, 1941, (2 folders)
    - 1942-1944, (4 folders) (Box 1351)
    - 1945-1947, (4 folders) (Box 1352)
    - 1948-1949, (4 folders) (Box 1353)
    - 1950-1951, (4 folders) (Box 1354)
  - Sky Farm, Warren County, Ohio (Box 1355)
    - 1922-1953, (3 folders)
    - Finch, Roy, 1934-1945
  - Taft family (Box 1356)
    - Taft, Charles Phelps, estate papers
      - 1939-1952, (4 folders)
      - 1942 (Box 1357)
    - Taft, Helen Herron, estate papers
      - 1938-1945, (2 folders)
      - 1951 (Box 1358)
      - Accounts and receipts, 1940-1953, (3 folders)
      - Canadian matters, 1943-1946 (Box 1359)
      - Closing, 1944
      - Financial statements, 1941-1942, (3 folders)
      - General (Box 1360)
        - 1936-1941, (5 folders)
        - 1942-1943 (Box 1361)
      - Insurance, 1940-1945
      - Inventory of personal property, 1943-1945
      - Mortgages
        - 1936-1946, (3 folders)
        - A-F, 1929-1949, (5 folders) (Box 1362)
        - G-M, 1933-1947, (4 folders) (Box 1363)
      - Real estate, 1934-1940, (2 folders)
      - Receipts, 1939-1943, (2 folders) (Box 1364)
      - Stock transfers, 1944
      - Stocks and bonds
        - 1936-1939, (3 folders)
        - 1940-1941 (Box 1365)
      - Taxes
        - Income, 1939-1948
        - Miscellaneous, 1940-1948
        - Personal property, 1939-1940
      - Valuation data, 1943-1946
    - Taft, Martha Bowers (Box 1366)
      - 1928-1950, (4 folders)
      - 1948-1950 (Box 1367)
      - Chicago, Ill., property, 1942-1924
      - General, 1937-1944
      - Industrial Commission of Ohio, 1939
      - Taxes, income and intangible, 1929-1942, (3 folders)
    - Taft, Robert A. (Box 1368)
      - Bank statements
        - Central Trust Co., Cincinnati, Ohio, 1947-1953, (3 folders)
        - First National Bank of Cincinnati, 1946-1953, (3 folders) (Box 1369)
        - Riggs National Bank, Washington, D.C. (Box 1370)
          - 1946-1951, (4 folders)
          - 1952-1953 (Box 1371)
      - Check stubs
        - Central Trust Co., Cincinnati, Ohio, 1936-1953
        - First National Bank of Cincinnati, 1941-1951, (2 folders) (Box 1372)
        - Riggs National Bank, Washington, D.C.
          - 1937-1938
          - 1940-1949, (3 folders) (Box 1373)
          - 1949-1950 (Box 1374)
          - Miscellaneous, 1938-1939
      - Cotton Oil Co., 1947-1952
      - Current Finances
        - 1934, (2 folders)
        - 1935 (Box 1375)
      - Estate papers
        - 1944-1953, (4 folders)
        - Casey, Robert P., 1947 (Box 1376)
      - General, 1945-1953
      - Insurance, 1948-1953
      - Investments, 1935
      - Miscellaneous financial notes, 1919, 1936-1952
      - Office and personal, 1942-1948
      - Passport
      - Personal finances
        - 1936
        - 1937-1953, (4 folders) (Box 1377)
        - 1944-1952, (4 folders) (Box 1378)
      - Petition, declaration of candidacy for Republican presidential nomination, 1952
      - Securities, 1936-1953
      - Social Security deductions and tax reports, 1953 (Box 1379)
      - Taft, Helen Herron, 1933, (2 folders)
      - Taft School, Watertown, Conn., 1944-1952
      - Taft, Stettinius and Hollister (law firm), Cincinnati
        - 1944-1953, (2 folders)
        - Financial statements, 1936-1943, (2 folders) (Box 1380)
        - Miscellaneous, 1941-1943
      - Taxes
        - Income
          - 1927-1951, (3 folders)
          - 1951-1953 (Box 1381)
          - Board of Tax Appeals, 1931
          - Protests, 1927-1932
        - Income and intangible
          - 1933-1942, (3 folders)
          - 1939-1942 (Box 1382)
      - Trial balances, 1921-1922
      - Trip abroad, 1948
      - Washington, D.C., residences, 1940-1953, (2 folders)
  - Wilson, Thomas (grandfather of Martha Bowers Taft), estate papers, 1937-1951, (4 folders) (Box 1383)
- Miscellany, 1907-1953 (Box 1384-1434)
  Appointment books, secretaries' notebooks, Christmas cards, property records in Canada, letters of condolence, material pertaining to Taft's association with Yale University, and miscellaneous material.
  - Appointment books and secretaries' notebooks (Box 1384)
    - 1940-1953
    - 1944-1948 (Box 1385)
    - 1949-1951 (Box 1386)
    - Undated (Box 1387)
  - Awards and certificates See also Oversize (Box 1388)
  - Christmas greetings cards (Box 1389)
    - 1944
      - A-G, (3 folders)
      - H-M, (4 folders) (Box 1390)
      - N-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1391)
    - 1952, (6 folders) (Box 1392)
  - Clippings (Box 1393)
    - 1939-1953, (4 folders)
  - Miscellany
    - Photostatic copies, 1949 See Oversize
    - Scrapbooks, 1940-1950 See Oversize, (3 vols.)
  - Congressional Record, vol. 95, parts 7 and 8, 1949 (Box 1394)
  - Death (Box 1395)
    - Letters of condolence, 1953
      - A-B, (5 folders)
      - B-C, (4 folders) (Box 1396)
      - C-D, (4 folders) (Box 1397)
      - D-F, (5 folders) (Box 1398)
      - F-G, (4 folders) (Box 1399)
      - H, (4 folders) (Box 1400)
      - H-J, (4 folders) (Box 1401)
      - K-L, (4 folders) (Box 1402)
      - L-M, (4 folders) (Box 1403)
      - M-N, (4 folders) (Box 1404)
      - O-R, (5 folders) (Box 1405)
      - R-S, (3 folders) (Box 1406)
      - S, (4 folders) (Box 1407)
      - S-W, (4 folders) (Box 1408)
      - W-Z and miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 1409)
    - Obituaries, 1953